When we resist the devil with a lively, active faith, satan would flee before us.
A believer is one who believes what it takes to cast out satan.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, come out!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, out!
Out!
Come out!
In the mighty name of Jesus, out!
It takes the authority in the name Jesus to command satan and direct him where to go.
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
His power and authority have not stopped,
just because He is no longer visible in our midst.
Just as it was, so it is.
Can you see why the work of God is delicate?
This is a stiff opposition.
If you are not heard by God, you will be heard by satan.
If you cannot deliver her, she will deliver you.
This is to tell you that we are not fighting a natural situation.
Thank You, Jesus! Thank you, Man of God!
My name is Stella Erasmus. I'm from South Africa.
I was demon possessed.
Because of the demon inside of me, it was impossible for me
even to walk up to my husband, give him a hug and tell him I love him.
I couldn't do it.
All the things I want to do, I didn't do and all the things I didn't want to do, I do.
But then I came to The SCOAN.
While I was here, the prophet was walking up and down, praying for people.
The demon inside of me grabbed hold of the chair.
I wanted to attack Prophet T.B. Joshua but the authority of God
in him was so powerful, so mighty.
It was impossible.
He used the authority in God.
I was down on the floor and he delivered me from the demon.
I thank God that he delivered me from that demon.
Thank You, Jesus. I am free.
TESTIMONY TIME
We welcome you here to The SCOAN in Lagos, Nigeria, in Jesus' name.
Madam, please tell us your name and your age.
My name is Stella Erasmus. I am 37 years old.
We saw you at the prayer line yesterday being prayed for by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Can you explain to us why you were in the prayer line?
I was demon possessed.
The demon - his face was like a triangle and his eyes were far apart.
Where his eyes were, there were also horns -
they weren't long, whitish, with a grey stripe;
a thick grey stripe on each horn.
He had a long face and arms up till the ellbow.
Can I show you guys?
His arms were like this.
He couldn't move this part.
He could only move it the way I'm showing you now.
His hands were very big; they were too big for his body.
He had big hips.
The bones - there wasn't even flesh.
The bones were also white and dry - they were like dry bones; very dry.
He had very long legs and his feet were very big.
His hands and nails were very long.
His hands had wrinkles like on little babies' hands and were white.
He was just very ugly.
What were the things that this problem made you to do?
It was so easy for me to attract men and to seduce them.
When they passed me, they would look back - I just knew that.
My marriage was a total disaster.
I couldn't allow my husband to get near me.
Even when he touched me, it irritated me a lot.
I couldn't walk up to my husband to give him a hug
even though I felt inside that I wanted to hug him.
The desire was there to hug him but I couldn't get to him to hug him or even kiss him.
If he touched me, it felt as if I could scream at him and
say, "Stop it, I don't like it".
I also have children.
When they were playing around me - I love my children so much -
I might just start talking, it irritated me incredibly.
I would chase them away and tell them, "Just go outside and play
but not around where I am sitting!"
When Prophet T.B. Joshua came to pray for me,
I grabbed hold of my chair because I didn't want to jump up
but the demon inside of me wanted to attack the prophet.
At one moment the anger was so much inside of me.
I knew that if I could get to the prophet
with the authority I had in me, I could attack him
but because of the authority he had in Jesus Christ--
So you mean that during the prayer, you literally wanted to attack the prophet
because of the demon inside of you.
But then, you could not because of the authority of Jesus Christ
when the prophet was praying for you.
Tell us, how did it feel?
We saw how you tried many times to stand up. What stopped you?
What was it that actually stopped you from touching the prophet?
The authority in his voice that he has in Jesus Christ.
I couldn't even look at him.
It is just like you don't have control over your body.
I looked away; he just started to turn and I looked away.
I couldn't look at him - it is the presence of God. It is overwhelming.
Why could you actually not look at Prophet T.B. Joshua while the prayer was going on?
What did you see that would stop you from looking at Prophet T.B. Joshua?
It was the light of Jesus Christ in him.
When he told me to sit down, I couldn't resist.
It is like the Word of God says, "Every knee shall bow".
That's what happened there.
I just sat down because of the authority.
When the prophet prayed for me, there was no more anger inside of me.
It's a calmness inside of me.
Before, I was always in a hurry; I was all over the place.
But after the prayer, there is a calmness inside of me.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ! Hallelujah!
You mean, immediately after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
you felt that the demon left you and you felt a calmness,
a peace in your heart that you had not experienced before.
Yes. Thank You, Jesus.
Oh, that's wonderful! Let's clap for Jesus Christ! Hallelujah!
Now that Jesus Christ has set you free, tell us about your mind now.
Are you still having any of those negative thoughts you used to have?
No, there are no negative thoughts.
And you are free?
Yes, I am free!
Let's put our hands together for the miracle-working Jesus Christ!
Hallelujah!
My promise to God is to go and sin no more.
I would like to give advice to people outside there.
Please, if you don't have faith in the name of Jesus Christ, don't use it.
You can cause so much problems for yourself.
Read your Bible with devotion.
Don't use the name in vain.
Amen. That's a wonderful advice to everyone of us here.
We thank God for your life.
We thank Jesus that you are set free from this problem forever.
And we pray that God will give you the grace to continue to go and sin no more
as you promised, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.